{
  "Times 8": [
    {
      "question": "8 x 2",
      "choices": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 3",
      "choices": [15, 16, 1, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 4",
      "choices": [24, 25, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 5",
      "choices": [20, 25, 30, 35, 40, 45, 50, 55],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 6",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 7",
      "choices": [46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 8",
      "choices": [54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 9",
      "choices": [62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 10",
      "choices": [70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 8",
      "choices": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 8",
      "choices": [15, 16, 1, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 8",
      "choices": [24, 25, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 8",
      "choices": [20, 25, 30, 35, 40, 45, 50, 55],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 8",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 8",
      "choices": [46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 8",
      "choices": [54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 8",
      "choices": [62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 8",
      "choices": [70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 80
    }
  ],
  "Times 7": [
    {
      "question": "7 x 2",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 3",
      "choices": [15, 16, 1, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 4",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 5",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 6",
      "choices": [31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 7",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 8",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 9",
      "choices": [50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 61, 62, 63],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 10",
      "choices": [57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 7",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 7",
      "choices": [15, 16, 1, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 7",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 7",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 7",
      "choices": [31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 7",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 7",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 7",
      "choices": [50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 61, 62, 63],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 7",
      "choices": [57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 70
    }
  ],
  "Times 6": [
    {
      "question": "6 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 2",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 3",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 1, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 5",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 6",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 7",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 8",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 9",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 10",
      "choices": [36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 42, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 6",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 6",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 6",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 6",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 6",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 6",
      "choices": [16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 6",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 6",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 6",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 6",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 6",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 60
    }
  ],
  "Times 5": [
    {
      "question": "5 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 2",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 3",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 5",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 6",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 7",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 8",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 9",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 10",
      "choices": [36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 42, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 5",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 5",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 5",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 5",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 5",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 5",
      "choices": [16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 5",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 5",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 5",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 5",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 5",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 50
    }
  ],
  "Times 4": [
    {
      "question": "4 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 2",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 3",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 5",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 6",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 7",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 8",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 9",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 10",
      "choices": [36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 42, 44],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 11",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 12",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 4",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 4",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 4",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 4",
      "choices": [16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 4",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 4",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 4",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 4",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 4",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "11 x 4",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "12 x 4",
      "choices": [40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 48
    }
  ],
  "Multiplication": [
    {
      "question": "0 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 2",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 3",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 4",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 5",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 6",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 7",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 8",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 9",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 10",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 11",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "0 x 12",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "11 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "12 x 0",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 2",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 3",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 4",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 5",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 6",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 7",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 8",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 9",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 10",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 11",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "1 x 12",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "11 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "12 x 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 2",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 3",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 4",
      "choices": [2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 5",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 6",
      "choices": [7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 7",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 8",
      "choices": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 9",
      "choices": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 10",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 11",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "2 x 12",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 2",
      "choices": [2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 2",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 2",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 2",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 2",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 2",
      "choices": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 2",
      "choices": [16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 2",
      "choices": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "11 x 2",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "12 x 2",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 3",
      "choices": [4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 4",
      "choices": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 5",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 6",
      "choices": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 7",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 8",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 9",
      "choices": [25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 10",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 11",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "question": "3 x 12",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "4 x 3",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "5 x 3",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "6 x 3",
      "choices": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "7 x 3",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "8 x 3",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "9 x 3",
      "choices": [20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "10 x 3",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "11 x 3",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "question": "12 x 3",
      "choices": [30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 36
    }
  ],
  "Subtraction (minus 3)": [
    {
      "question": "3 - 3",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "4 - 3",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "5 - 3",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "6 - 3",
      "choices": [2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "7 - 3",
      "choices": [2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "8 - 3",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "9 - 3",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "10 - 3",
      "choices": [4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "11 - 3",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "12 - 3",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "13 - 3",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 10
    }
  ],
  "Subtraction (minus 2)": [
    {
      "question": "2 - 2",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "3 - 2",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "4 - 2",
      "choices": [2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "5 - 2",
      "choices": [2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "6 - 2",
      "choices": [2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "7 - 2",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "8 - 2",
      "choices": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "9 - 2",
      "choices": [4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "10 - 2",
      "choices": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 8
    }
  ],
  "Subtraction (minus 1)": [
    {
      "question": "1 - 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2],
      "take": 3,
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "2 - 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3],
      "take": 4,
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "3 - 1",
      "choices": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "4 - 1",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "5 - 1",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "6 - 1",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "7 - 1",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "8 - 1",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "9 - 1",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "10 - 1",
      "choices": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 9
    }
  ],
  "Addition (plus 10)": [
    {
      "question": "0 + 10",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 10",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 10",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 10",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 10",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 10",
      "choices": [11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 10",
      "choices": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 10",
      "choices": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 10",
      "choices": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 10",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 10",
      "choices": [11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 0",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 1",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 2",
      "choices": [11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 3",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 5",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 6",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 7",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 8",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 9",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 10",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 20
    }
  ],
  "Addition (plus 9)": [
    {
      "question": "0 + 9",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 9",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 9",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 9",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 9",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 9",
      "choices": [11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 9",
      "choices": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 9",
      "choices": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 9",
      "choices": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 9",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 9",
      "choices": [11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 0",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 1",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 2",
      "choices": [11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 3",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 5",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 6",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 7",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 8",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 9",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 10",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 19
    }
  ],
  "Addition (plus 8)": [
    {
      "question": "0 + 8",
      "choices": [7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 8",
      "choices": [7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 8",
      "choices": [8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 8",
      "choices": [8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 8",
      "choices": [8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 8",
      "choices": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 8",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 8",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 8",
      "choices": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 8",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 0",
      "choices": [8, 9, 10, 11, 12],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 1",
      "choices": [8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 2",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 3",
      "choices": [8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 4",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 5",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 6",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 7",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 8",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 9",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 10",
      "choices": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20],
      "take": 5,
      "answer": 18
    }
  ]
}
